Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/khắclâp-21487b145 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Test Cases
Test Planning
Java

Khắc Lập

Java backend dev at fpt software

Vietnam

Summary

Experienced Java Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the public relations and communications industry. Skilled in Java, Test Planning, HTML, Software Development, and JavaScript. Strong engineering professional graduated from học viện bưu chính viễn thông.

Experience

FPT Software

Developer

October 2018 - Present (3 years 2 months)

cầu giấy

Develop code online sýtem

Role: BA and dev

Framework: spring boot

Db: mysql

Sourse managerment: bitbugket, sourse tree.

Team size: 4

Fsoft

Java Web Developer

October 2015 - January 2018 (2 years 4 months)

Fsu17. R73

Experience:

- +Technology :Java, Jsp, struts 2, velocity , html, css, jquery, sql
- + Management source : git, Svn, redmime.
- + Tool: eclipse, sql developer, MySQL

All of Phase in project:

Analyst requirement of customer

Create basic design

Create detail design

Implement source code

Create FUT case

Execute FUT

Execute IT case

Education

học viện bửu chính viễn thông PTIT, Computer Software Engineering · (2011 - 2015)

Activity

11/23/2021, Viewed by Nga Lê (Lenka)